<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Calum Boal</title>
    <link>https://calumboal.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Calum Boal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 13:32:56 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://calumboal.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>gRPC Made Easy - Project Crobat</title>
      <link>https://calumboal.com/posts/grpc-made-easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 13:32:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://calumboal.com/posts/grpc-made-easy/</guid>
      <description>gRPC made easy - Project Crobat In this post, I will be going over the implementation of the gRPC API used by Project Crobat. I figured this would make a good post as gRPC is, in my opinion, very cool and the use-case employed by Project Crobat is simple enough to provide a real-world example of its usage.
Why gRPC So, you may be wondering why I&amp;rsquo;m even writing this post at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So you want to be a pentester?</title>
      <link>https://calumboal.com/posts/so-you-want-to-be-a-pentester/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://calumboal.com/posts/so-you-want-to-be-a-pentester/</guid>
      <description>The other day I posted on Twitter that my DMs were open to anyone who needed advice in their Cyber Security journey. Turns out there are a lot of you looking for advice. After receiving 200+ DMs I noticed that the majority of them are asking similar questions. As a result, I figured it&amp;rsquo;d be best to write a blog post to answer these questions since it&amp;rsquo;ll take me forever to answer everyone individually, and this way I can provide high-quality answers to all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searching Project Sonar - Creating a fast API for large datasets</title>
      <link>https://calumboal.com/posts/project-sonar-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 14:47:59 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://calumboal.com/posts/project-sonar-api/</guid>
      <description>Making Project Sonar Searchable This blog outlines my recent efforts to make Project Sonar a practical source of DNS data when performing security assessments or bug hunting.
 If you don&amp;rsquo;t care for the rationale or technical details discussed in this blog, the API is currently available free of charge and can be accessed here: https://sonar.omnisint.io
Additionally, a command-line client has been implemented, which can be obtained by running the following command:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Ab)using Kerberos from Linux</title>
      <link>https://calumboal.com/posts/abusing-kerberos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 18:32:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://calumboal.com/posts/abusing-kerberos/</guid>
      <description>This post aims to provide an overview of tooling available to perform common Kerberos abuse techniques from Linux. While this blog will not go into great detail about how the attacks which utilize these techniques work, references will be provided to high-quality blog posts detailing common Kerberos attacks.
Kerberos Overview Before we jump into it, a brief preface shall be provided regarding the function of Kerberos within Active Directory, and why it&amp;rsquo;s beneficial to be fluent in Kerberos manipulation when performing penetration tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Persistent Collaborator</title>
      <link>https://calumboal.com/posts/persistent-collaborator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 21:46:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://calumboal.com/posts/persistent-collaborator/</guid>
      <description>How I gained persistent access to Burp’s Collaborator Sessions In this write up, I set out an easy way to gain persistent access to Burp Suite’s Collaborator sessions. Previously these were thought to be volatile, and to disappear once the current instance of the Collaborator client is closed.
What is Burp Suite Collaborator? The Collaborator client in Burp allows you to generate Collaborator links and monitor DNS, HTTP, and SMTP interactions made by external services.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
