<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Calum Boal</title>
    <link>https://calumboal.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Calum Boal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 18:32:56 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://calumboal.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>(Ab)using Kerberos from Linux</title>
      <link>https://calumboal.com/posts/abusing-kerberos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 18:32:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://calumboal.com/posts/abusing-kerberos/</guid>
      <description>This post aims to provide an overview of tooling available to perform common Kerberos abuse techniques from Linux. While this blog will not go into great detail about how the attacks which utilize these techniques work, references will be provided to high-quality blog posts detailing common Kerberos attacks.
Kerberos Overview Before we jump into it, a brief preface shall be provided regarding the function of Kerberos within Active Directory, and why it&amp;rsquo;s beneficial to be fluent in Kerberos manipulation when performing penetration tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Persistent Collaborator</title>
      <link>https://calumboal.com/posts/persistent-collaborator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 21:46:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://calumboal.com/posts/persistent-collaborator/</guid>
      <description>How I gained persistent access to Burp’s Collaborator Sessions In this write up, I set out an easy way to gain persistent access to Burp Suite’s Collaborator sessions. Previously these were thought to be volatile, and to disappear once the current instance of the Collaborator client is closed.
What is Burp Suite Collaborator? The Collaborator client in Burp allows you to generate Collaborator links and monitor DNS, HTTP, and SMTP interactions made by external services.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>